http://www.iclei.org/en/privacy_policy.html

ICLEI
By using this website, you consent to its use of cookies.
Privacy policy
1. Introduction1.1 This privacy policy notice applies to ICLEI.org and any other ICLEI websites, forms, or services, in addition to any event organized by ICLEI or general interactions with ICLEI or its representatives. Together with the user agreements that ICLEI websites, events, or services might have, this privacy policy governs ICLEI´s data collection and use.1.2 For the purpose of the EU 2016 General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR"), ICLEI - Local Governments for Sustainability e.V. (World Secretariat), based in Kaiser- Friedrich- Straße 7,53113 Bonn, Germany, (thereafter ICLEI e.V), acts as data controller.1.3 ICLEI does not have any responsibility on how other platforms and websites outside of the ICLEI´s controlled websites, use and share users´ personal information, even if those platforms / websites have a link on or from the ICLEI website. It is the responsibility of the users to check in each specific case if other websites provide a safe environment for their personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.2. Personal data collected by use of Cookies2.1 ICLEI websites might collect internet Cookies from all its users. The purpose of Cookies is to improve your online experience on our website by informing the webserver that you have returned to a specific page, which allows it to load the page faster with your personal features and to save time. Cookies are text files created from the moment you download the webpage and is stored on your computer by a webpage server. They are uniquely assigned to you and can exclusively be read by the webserver in the same domain which issued the Cookie. They cannot be used to runs programs or viruses.2.2 Examples of Cookies are the Google analytic tools, used for ICLEI websites to collect information about your computer that is automatically provided to its server. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by ICLEI for the operation of its websites, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding uses of ICLEI websites.2.3 You have the ability to accept or decline Cookies. If you choose to decline Cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive feature provided by our websites.3. Collected data collected from registered users3.1 ICLEI may collect, through the registration process to one of its website, through the registration to one of its newsletters, through the registration to one of its virtual events and webinars, through the registration and/or participation to an ICLEI in person event through personal communication with ICLEI or one of its representatives, and through any services that ICLEI provides, the following personal information:First NameLast NameOrganizationJob titleEmailOffice phone numberOrganization AddressPhotos3.2 In case of registration on a website, an identification number is assigned to register users. This user id can help track any changes requested by the user when submitting data on one of our website which allows uploading.3.3 Digital events organized by ICLEI are hosted on third parties platform. All interaction with these platforms in the context of a digital event organized will be covered by the privacy policy of the said platform.3.4 In this case of communication by email with ICLEI, your personal information will be collected to enable to deliver the services you have requested.4. Use of personal data4.1 Personal data are used exclusively for the legitimate purpose for which they were collected (services provided by ICLEI, newsletter, in person and virtual events and webinars, communication with ICLEI) or for the good functioning of the websites. ICLEI may use your personal data for the following:4.1.1 Personal data resulting from cookies:To adapt the presentation of the content of the ICLEI website in order to align it with the technical specifications of your computer.To get to know how ICLEI e.V. can improve services based on how you use them.4.1.2 Personal data provided through registration form, or through any kind of services provided by ICLEI:To contact you for communications related to the services provided by ICLEI.To provide you with specific information, support or other requested services.To communicate with you about a meeting, conference or event related to ICLEI, or our partners.To get feedback or input from you.For any other interactions that you may have with ICLEI.4.1.3 Photos collected or taken by ICLEI in the context of an event might be used for internal and external communication related to the event.4.1.4 Recordings of ICLEI virtual events and webinars might be used for internal and external communication related to the event.4.1.5 Personal data provided by registering to a newsletter will only be used for the purpose of sending you the newsletter you registered to.4.2 ICLEI might also use your personal data for the purposes of the pursue of its legitimate interests. ICLEI´s legitimate interests are environmental protection; nature protection and development assistance, especially the improvement of local and global environmental conditions by supporting local programs and projects for environmental protection; nature protection and sustainable development worldwide, in developed as well as in developing countries.Therefore, ICLEI uses your personal data to communicate with you in the context of the following activities:(a) Mobilize and provide support to local-level initiatives that address specific priority problems of local and global significance.(b) Help develop and strengthen local capacity and expertise.(c) Support networking among and exchange of experiences between local governments, especially between developing and industrialized countries.(d) Work with groups of local governments and partner organizations in order to research, develop, pilot and implement local initiatives for sustainability.(e) Function as a clearinghouse for information, and as a training center, on local sustainable development and environmental policies and programs.(f) Provide technical support services and consultancy to aid the implementation of local sustainable development and environmental policies and programs.(g) Evaluate and report on the impacts of local actions.In the context of the above missions, ICLEI might also transfer your personal data to its partners and donors.4.3 ICLEI will never use your personal data for any commercial use.4.4 ICLEI will not place your personal data on any mailing list that you do not opt-in to.5. Disclosure of personal dataICLEI does not use or disclose your personal data without your explicit consent, except for the following situations:In cases where disclosure is required by law.In good faith, when disclosure is made necessary to protect the ICLEI´s right of property, and/or the personal safety of its users or the public.6. Data Storage6.1 Personal Data are stored in the servers of ICLEI e.V., based in Germany, and are therefore subject to the German Federal Law on Personal Data(“Bundesdatenschutzgesetz”), as currently amended, and to the 2016 EU General Data Protection Regulation.6.2 ICLEI e.V. will hold your personal data on its servers for as long as needed to achieve its legitimate purposes. The appropriate duration of retention of personal data is determined by this, as well as, by their nature and sensitivity, also considering an assessment of the risk of unauthorized use or disclosure of those personal data. ICLEI e.V. will automatically delete all data which is no longer considered relevant for its purposes.6.3 ICLEI e.V. is committed to the security of your data and consequently takes all appropriate measures to prevent the loss of your data or access without authorization. Access to personal data is strictly restricted to a limited number of ICLEI staffs which are subject to a duty of confidentiality.6.4 In the unlikely event of a data security breach, ICLEI e.V. will promptly notify you and take all the necessary measures to protect your data.7. Rights on your personal data7.1 The 2016 EU General Data Protection Regulation provides you with the following rights over your personal data:Access your personal data.Require the correction of any mistakes in your personal data.Request the data controller to delete all your personal data from our servers (right to be forgotten).Demand the transfer of all your personal data to a third party (data portability).Forbid use of your personal data for direct marketing.Restrict the use of your personal data to certain conditions.Claim compensation for damages resulting from a violation of any applicable personal data protection laws.7.2 For any request concerning your rights please contact our personal data officer (privacy@iclei.org).7.3 You have the right to lodge a claim for compensation at the data protection supervisory authority where you are located or where we are based (Landesbeauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit Nordrhein-Wesphalien).8. Change to the privacy policyAny change to this privacy policy notice will be published on the ICLEI websites and registered users will be notified per email.9. ContactAll questions or requests regarding the ICLEI personal data policy can be addressed to privacy@iclei.org.
ICLEI – Local Governments for Sustainability is a global network of more than 1,750 local and regional governments committed to sustainable urban development.
Contact Us
Kaiser-Friedrich-Str. 7 53113 Bonn | Germany Tel. +49-228 / 97 62 99-00
Subscribe to our iNews
Why ICLEI
Our approach
Our work
Our network
Take action
Join
Get involved
F.+49-228/97 62 99-01
Email:
Membership inquiries:membership(at)iclei.org
Communications inquiries:media(at)iclei.org
Climate inquiries:climate.center(at)iclei.org
Events inquiries:capacity.center(at)iclei.org
General inquiries:iclei.ws(at)iclei.org
www.iclei.org
EUROPE
European Secretariat
Berlin Office
St. Oberholz ROS Team Room 4.02 Rosenthaler Str. 72a10119 Berlin,Germany
T: +49 761 36 89 2-0
F: +49 761 36 89 2-19
E: berlin-office(at)iclei.org
Africa secretariat
Physical address:3 Knowledge ParkCentury CityCape Town8001South Africa
Postal address:PO Box 5319Tygervalley7536South Africa
T. +27 21 202 0381
E. iclei-africa(at)iclei.org
africa.iclei.org
north america
Canada Office
401 Richmond St. WStudio 204Toronto, OntarioM5V 3A8, Canada
T: 1-647/728-4308
Mexico, Central American and Caribbean Secretariat
Eje Central Lazaro Cardenas 13 Building Miguel Abed, Floor 5 Of. 506 and 507,Col. Centro, CP 06050 Del.Cuauhtemoc, Mexico City, Mexico
T: +52 55 5345 3000 xt 5622 and 5623
E: iclei-colombia(at)iclei.org
E: iclei-colombia(at)iclei.org
iclei.org.mx/
Colombia Office
Área Metropolitana del Valle de AburráCarrera 53 N° 40A - 31Medellín,Antioquia – Colombia
T: +52 55 5345 3000 xt 5622 and 5623
E: iclei-colombia(at)iclei.org
iclei.org.mx/
ICLEI Argentina
Boulevard Gálvez, 1150 Planta Alta.Santa Fe, Argentina.
E: iclei-argentina(at)iclei.org
South America
South American Secretariat
Rua Marquês de Itu 70, 14° andar.São Paulo, SP, BrasilCEP 01223-000
T: +55-11 / 5084-3079
E: iclei-sams(at)iclei.org
www.sams.iclei.org
Colombia Office
Carrera 53 N° 40A - 31, Medellín, Antioquia – Colombia
T: +52 55 5345 3000 xt 5622 and 5623
E: iclei-colombia(at)iclei.org
E: iclei-colombia(at)iclei.org
South Asia Secretariat
C-3, Lower Ground Floor Green Park Extension New Delhi - 110016, India
T: +91 11 4106 7220
F: +91 11 4106 7221
E: iclei-southasia(at)iclei.org
southasia.iclei.org
Southern Center
Door No. 6-3-596/47/2Sri Venkata Ramana ColonyHyderabad 500 004Andhra Pradesh
T: +91 - 40 / 40034004/5/6/8
F: +91 - 40 / 40034011
E: iclei-southasia(at)iclei.org
east asia
East Asia Secretariat
14/F, Seoul Global Center Building, 38 Jongno, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea (110-110)
T: +82-2-3789-0496
F: +82-2-3789-0497
E: iclei-eastasia(at)iclei.org
eastasia.iclei.org
Japan Office
1-14-2 Nishi-Shimbashi,Minato-kuTokyo, Japan 105-0003
T: +81-3/6205-8415
F: +81-3/3797-1906
E: iclei-japan(at)iclei.org
japan.iclei.org
Kaohsiung Capacity Center
4F. No.436, Daye N. Rd. Xiaogang Dist. Kaohsiung City 812Taiwan (R.O.C.)
T: +886 987 905 927
kcc.iclei.org
Korea Office
(16429) 3F, Suwon Research Institute,
126, Suin-ro, Gwonseon-gu, Suwon-si, Gyeonggi-do, Republic of Korea
T: +82-31-255-3257
F: +82-31-256-3257
E: iclei-korea(at)iclei.org
www.icleikorea.org
Beijing Office
B1010 Xiaoyun Center, No. 15Beijing 100125,China
E: iclei-china(at)iclei.org
southeast asia
Southeast Asia Secretariat
c/o The Manila Observatory Ateneo de Manila University Campus Loyola Heights, Quezon City 1101 Manila, Philippines
T:+63-2/426-0851; 4265921 to 23
F: +63-2/426-0851
E: iclei-seasia(at)iclei.org
seas.iclei.org
ICLEI Indonesia Project Office
Rasuna Office Park III WO. 06-09 Komplek Rasuna Epicentrum Jl. Taman Rasuna Selatan, Kuningan DKI Jakarta, 12960, Indonesia
E: iclei-indonesia(at)iclei.org
oceania
Oceania Secretariat
Level 1, 200 Little Collins Street Melbourne, Victoria 3000, Australia
T:+61 3 9639 8688
F:+61-3/9639-8677
E: oceania(at)iclei.org
icleioceania.org
ICLEI World Congress 2018
Tabs Opener
agenda
practical info
resources
register
Agenda
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Aenean commodo ligula eget dolor. Aenean massa. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec quam felis, ultricies nec, pellentesque eu, pretium quis, sem. Nulla consequat massa quis enim. Donec pede justo, fringilla vel, aliquet nec, vulputate eget, arcu. In enim justo, rhoncus ut, imperdiet a, venenatis vitae, justo. Nullam dictum felis eu pede mollis pretium. Integer tincidunt. Cras dapibus. Vivamus elementum semper nisi. Aenean vulputate eleifend tellus. Aenean leo ligula, porttitor eu, consequat vitae, eleifend ac, enim. Aliquam lorem ante, dapibus in, viverra quis, feugiat a, tellus. Phasellus viverra nulla ut metus varius laoreet. Quisque rutrum. Aenean imperdiet. Etiam ultricies nisi vel augue. Curabitur ullamcorper ultricies nisi. Nam eget dui. Etiam rhoncus. Maecenas tempus, tellus eget condimentum rhoncus, sem quam semper libero, sit amet adipiscing sem neque sed ipsum.
practical info
resources
register
Associate Partnership
Tabs Opener
About
Rates and Dues
Application Form
Contact
Associate Partnership is available to non-governmental organizations, universities, state and national government agencies and not-for-profit research institutions. The purpose of Associate Partnership is to facilitate dialogues between local governments and these partners, to provide knowledge transfer in line with ICLEI's Mission and Charter, and an avenue for which partners can support ICLEI's work and mandate.
HARNESS the power of the ICLEI Network!
" Governments need to give (the sense of) direction, as Business leaders we don't make the wind, we sail the boats. So policy should set the winds in the right directions if you want the boat going fast to the right harbor."
Philippe Joubert
Senior Advisor, World Business Council on Sustainable Development
Click here to view a full list of our associate partners
All India Institute of Local Self Government
Center for Environmental Studies Foundation
Central New York Regional Planning and Development Board
China Center for Urban Development (CCUD)
Got any questions? I will be happy to assist. Please contact me at iclei(at)iclei.org
